The craziest part about success is how
normal it starts to feel. Welcome to a
night in my life.
Diplomatic immunity. [__] them. All that
peace and that unity. All that weak [__]
will ruin me. [__] them. Yeah. Cuz
[__] started talking to me like I'm
slowing down. Opinions over statistics
of course
journalist.
[Music]
>> So honestly it's a lovehate relationship
with my night routine. It has definitely
changed over the last 4 years. I've been
a millionaire probably for the last 5
years. And if you would have asked me
what my night routine was when I was a
21-year-old millionaire, it'd be very
different than what it is now. Now I
feel more mature and a lot more locked
in 100%. That's probably why I've become
so much more richer. And uh honestly
starts off every single night in the
sauna. Nobody wants to come in the sauna
with me. So I'm in here by myself for
like 20 30 minutes kind of prepping
myself for London session. You guys know
I trade London session every single
night and I got to be awake till like
3:00 4 in the morning. So the sauna
keeps me up. Right now it's
sauna does that to me. Right now it's
9:20 in the afternoon Thursday night.
I'll be in here for 20 minutes. And
while the majority of the world right
now is probably going to sleep because
they have to wake up tomorrow early to
go to work, I'm literally getting ready
to stay awake all night. Everybody's
sleeping. I'm grinding. And uh I think
that's why I've become so successful
because I'm doing what 99% of people
don't want to do. Nobody wants to be
awake in the middle of the night, but I
want to have two [__] Bugatti. So, I
got to do what I got to do. So, we're
going to be in here probably for another
10 to 15 minutes and check up on our
trade and see where the night takes us.
This is a realistic raw night in my
life. What it looks like every single
night.
>> Oh, and I also want to cancel out a lot
of people's expectations. So, people
might be thinking, yo, Alex is probably
going to go out like spend money, go
club,
>> and no, no, no, no. Like, I literally
try and eliminate as many possible
distractions as I can every single night
so I can be as locked in as I possibly
could be. Like if I'm going to be
risking $1, $150,000 per trade, I want
to have no distractions. I want to make
sure the decision that I'm going to be
taking on the trade is 100% good and
that I'm taking the best possible trade
setup that I can. So that's why I kind
of built my own compound here, my own
sauna in my house, basketball court,
gym. I even have like my own chicken
eggs in the back so I don't even have to
go grocery shopping. I just get fresh
eggs every single day. So yeah, my night
routine now has definitely changed from
when I was 21. I look back at some old
videos sometimes and I'm like, "Dude,
what the [__] was I doing?" And to all
my 19, 20, 21 year olds that are just
touching money or anybody that's really
touching money at any point in your
life, right? Cuz I think this happens
when you first start touching money or
making money, I get it. You want to go
spend it. You want to go live it up. You
want to make sure that it's real. But,
you know, I've realized now after being
a millionaire for the last four years,
nearly five years, that
spending money on stupid [__] does not
make you a millionaire. makes you a
dumbass. Like I used to be the guy with
the diamond chains, diamond watches,
flashy Gucci LV. Yeah. No, I Yeah. No,
not not anymore. I'll walk around with a
black t-shirt probably with a hole in
it. But I'm getting out of a $3 million
hyper car that's, you know, appreciating
a price and I have multiple eight
figures in real estate in my trading
account. And I don't know, as I'm making
this video right now and like as I was
looking back at old videos, I'm like,
dude, I was a [__] kid. Like I was
really a kid touching millions of
dollars. And I'm glad that I matured and
that I was actually able to grow from
that. I know a lot of people that made
money and they lost it all. How many
traders out there do you know that
actually made some money and then they
ended up in a worse spot than where they
originally were because they don't know
how to maintain it and scale it? I got
pretty lucky that I understood that to
grow money you need to reinvest it and
you can't really spend it all. And I'd
say that that is what led me to where I
am right now to be an like bro I bro
I've set myself up to the point where I
don't have to work for the next 15 years
like and I'm chilling. And I've realized
that you don't you don't get taught
that. You almost have to like learn it.
And some people end up never learning it
and they can never come back because
like once you're at that high making all
that money so easily and you lose it,
you almost you almost just forget,
right? you forget what you had to do to
get there and it just becomes like you
almost become delusional but in the
wrong way. Now at the point where I am
now, I understand not only how to keep
it, how to scale it and multiply. And
now I'm I'm grateful for the lessons
that life gave me and that I didn't [__]
up because I would definitely be in a
worse position. Like, bro, I'd be
[__] bro. I know what it is that I
crash a Bugatti and then I go buy
another $3 million car like a month
after. you know, if if you're spending
equally as much as you're making every
single month, you can never do that. So,
I don't know. I'm just glad that I'm
making this video now rather than when I
was 21 because I feel like I would have
set false expectations on how to
actually become successful and how to
actually build a routine to make money,
whether it's in a business, life, or
trading. And this is just the real raw
reality version of it. So, let's see
where it goes.
I hate hate being barefoot.
>> All right, so little trade up there
right now. So
bring my desk up. I don't want to sit
down. I'm not [__] sweaty on the
chair. Bro, honestly, I love my compound
right here. Yo, check this out. I have
my outdoor office. I have the basketball
court, the sauna we just came out of,
and then right here, my gym. Bro, like I
have no excuses on why to not be
healthy, successful, just all around
good. Yo, honestly, I I can live in
here. Just like in here alone, I could
sleep on that couch right there. Yo,
funny enough, that couch is actually Oh,
no. I can't say. Let's say that couch
that couch in specific.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that I I bought it off him.
This is a famous rapper's couch. I went
to his house accidentally, like I just
got invited and I'm like, "Yo, I like
your [__] couch." He's like, "Bro,
you sure?" I'm like, "Dude, I like your
couch. Give me your couch." He's like,
"No, bro. You can go buy it." And I'm
like, "Yo, dude, I want your couch. Sell
me your couch." He's like, "No, bro.
can't buy my couch. I paid 50 grand for
it. I'm like, I'll give you 70 grand.
Sold. Now it's here. Yeah. I mean, if I
overpaid for it, don't remind me. All
right. Just take it off of impulse just
to say I have their couch here. So,
quick trade update. Right now, we are up
$69,000.
And usually I I would hide my trade
balance before like because I've had,
you know, bigger balances than 3
million. And I would do it just because
people would think that it was fake and
people would be like, "Yo, your account
is not real." Now, I'm at the point go
[__] You think it's fake? Go [__]
yourself, right? I'm making money. I
don't give a [__] NZDUSD, we took it
last night pretty much and right now
it's having a beautiful retracement into
this area. I think it's creating a left
head right shoulder and I think tonight
in London session, it's going to have a
pretty significant push to the downside.
GBP CAD on the other hand, we entered
all the way up here, had a massive 1
to6, and then I decided to be a hero and
continue to hold and price came back. We
have another trade cooking up right now
which is S&P 500. Thank thank god thank
god we did not take that [__] cuz we
would have gotten our stop loss it. So
realistically we're just going to keep
holding NZDUSD
or we are up technically we're like just
20 grand in that position. I'm going to
go have fun with my demo profits. But
right now it's exactly 9:39 p.m. So my
boys come over every single night right
around now like 9:30 10:00 we play
basketball. We're going to do a little
barbecue tonight and see where the night
takes us. Every single night I hit
cardio sauna and prep myself for London
session. So, let's go.
>> Yo, if Drake could wear this [__] so
can I, right? Yeah,
>> cuz there's a picture of Drake wearing
one of these shits backwards, too.
>> I just think you try to break it.
>> Yo, so look. Ready to get our game on,
right? I bet you guys Oh, you almost I
almost I swear to God almost got a
cramp.
>> Oh my god, bro. I swear to God,
>> bro. You're supposed to 25 giving
excuses.
>> No, no, I'm 24.
>> No, no. He secretly 32. He's secretly
32. Don't lie.
>> Think all his followers thinks he's
30ome.
>> Tom, you're from 1983.
>> No,
you got to send your birth to
>> Yo, the other day I almost posted my ID
just to prove a point.
>> You should. You should.
>> Yeah, but then I'm like, "Okay, let me
blur my address." But then there's so
many scammers out there that they would
have probably like taken the picture of
my ID and made another ID. I'm like, you
know what? It's not even worth proving
the point. But what matters is I got
these on today. I bet you guys don't
have these on.
>> Still going to lose.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> Yo, which which color is more sus? The
pink Elva or the pink Porsche. All
right. So, this is George's Porsche. And
um pink is the new wave. You guys are
asleep on pink.
>> That's what I'm saying. And honestly,
let's go bottle.
Told you guys I was 6'2.
Don't
>> keep the frame up there.
My
>> face. You got to put it like a little
bit higher.
>> I want to do like
>> almost took out your head.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Go, go, go.
>> Is it Is this how the Brown feels?
>> Like that?
>> Yeah.
[Laughter]
I pulled the muscle on my butt cheek.
>> Oh, bro.
>> First it was this guy with the cal and
now your butt cheek.
>> Look at these juicy arms.
>> Oh my god.
>> He's all white and [__]
>> No. All right, let's play.
>> He feels the fear. So that's why he's
sitting down there.
>> All right,
>> brother. We won.
>> That's one zip. Best bet. Two out of
three. Let's go.
>> Light work.
>> Bet. Bet right now. Want to bet?
>> Go bet.
>> Checks over.
>> No. No. No. It's cuz you didn't stay on
me, bro. I got it. I got you. Checks
over stripes.
>> [__] I got you. I got you.
>> Checks over stripes.
>> I got you.
Take five. Take five.
>> Strike.
I'm done. Tired.
>> Wait. Wait. Wait. Let me tell you how
it's done. Let me show you how it's
done.
>> What is it?
>> Checks over strikes.
>> I'm out.
[Music]
Oh yeah.
>> Hey [__]
burn.
>> It's like that, bro.
>> Look like you don't know what you're
doing, bro.
>> Trust me, I do this [__] every night,
bro. She'll wag you everything, buddy.
This looks like one of those Burger King
commercials when they throw the the
burger on the grill and it just does
that effect.
>> You want to see that effect right now?
Hold up. Let's do it slow motion.
Let it chill for a little bit. Let it
chill for a little bit. Let it settle.
>> I know. I know.
>> Off the grill.
>> No pressure.
>> No pressure. Off the grill.
>> Set and forget, brother. Now we just
[__] light it up.
Oh, here
we're down.
>> Not bad. Not bad. We've been worse. Not
bad.
>> You want to You want to light yours?
>> How do I light it?
>> So, you got to get four of them. Five.
[Music]
You just grab the one that he just
finished so you can get the sauce. You
know, you heat it up.
>> [__]
>> [__] hurt you, bro.
>> No. No. Put it down. Put it down. Put it
down. No. No. No. This. This. This. This
this.
>> Other way. So,
>> no. No. The other way. Like that. Like
that.
>> Yeah, buddy.
>> Mhm.
It tastes strong, bro.
>> This is a This is a man's cigar right
here, bro.
>> The cigar is that one.
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah,
>> bro. You're still trying to light up the
tobacco.
>> You want to do the Cuban way? You like
that?
>> No.
>> No. That's that that's [__] bro. What
do you mean?
>> [__]
>> That's how everybody All right. All
right. Cigarette.
>> But you got to go on that side. You got
to go in.
>> Oh.
All right. So, this is perfect now.
It needs to be a little bit more like I
feel it. It's got to be a little bit
harder.
>> I'm very sure there's going to be some
type of meat expert telling you that you
did it wrong.
>> I hear what I got to say to them.
>> [__] you.
What type of meat expert though?
>> I'm just saying
>> it's going to be super pink on the
inside. That's fine.
>> That's what she said.
>> Aren't you married, man?
>> Oh,
the cigar is good.
>> Wait, where's your ring?
>> I'm not married, bro.
>> Oh, not yet.
>> Not yet. I'm engaged.
>> That's how you know you're old when
you're engaged.
Bro, there's people that are engaged
like at 20 years old
>> and then they got divorced.
>> That's true. That's true. All my friends
started to have babies. I feel old as
[__]
>> Going to baby showers, gender reveals
every month.
>> It went from pizzas to [__] baby
showers.
>> Yeah, that [__] turned hella fast, bro.
>> Alex is going through that phase right
now. He's like, "Fuck." You multiple
weddings, huh?
>> I've gone to like couple Yeah, like
three, four.
>> Have you been bachelor on any?
>> No. Ah,
>> he's he is on mine. We're going to
repeat the hangover.
>> But where?
>> Thailand.
>> Watch out with the lady boys.
>> That's your vibe, though.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no.
>> Little game of Thailand where you let
never hurt anybody.
>> Don't get scared, bro. It's going to be
super pink inside,
>> bro. Inside's going to be super pink
right now.
>> That's the vibe.
>> No, bro. That's perfect. That's Bro,
that's medium rare. That's good,
>> bro.
>> We chilling. Oh, hold on. [__] it up.
>> All right. Honestly, this is how I like
it. I could do one flip for you guys if
you guys like. Who would want a little
bit more? This to me is perfect.
>> That's perfect.
>> You want that?
>> I think
>> I think one more flip. One more.
>> One more.
>> One more flip.
>> One more set and forget.
>> I think that's what happened. He didn't
set and forget on that.
>> He just like He just said it, but he
didn't forget it.
Waiting the right.
[Music]
Yo, what else do I do at [__] 1:30 in
the morning, bro? Like, [__] We're up
55 grand now. So, yeah, trades aren't
looking that good. 1:30 in the morning.
Half of the world is asleep right now
and we're up staring at a computer. So,
you choose what you want to be doing.
You're probably slobbering right now in
bed and I am doing cat videos trying to
keep myself up to make a decision, a
crucial decision right now. Do I
continue to hold my position or do I
close? And we might close cuz honestly
we were just up 200 grand and now we're
up 50 grand. So I might just take my 50
grand. So I take my 3-week winning
streak and we call it that. And I do see
major downside potential on both of
these markets. But I don't see it
heading into the last good session of
the week. So the market moves
realistically like three and a half days
out of the week. Friday is like the
slowest moving day. So I might just take
my 50k run, call it a 3WE winning streak
and come back next week. A lot of people
that trade and had a slow week to try
and like think that they can hero it and
catch a good trade before the market
closes. Like I need to make something
before the market closes so I can get my
profits for the week. That's not how it
goes, boys. The market's moving slow.
The market's moving slow. There's
nothing you can do about it. Us traders,
our job is literally to sit here and
react off of the what the market shows
us. If the market is giving us nothing,
we do nothing. Does this suck? Do you
think I want to be awake right now just
staring at the computer? No. I would
much rather be sleeping. But I I love
what I do and I enjoy the journey of it.
And I learn to have fun with the pros
and the cons. The pros is I get to do
fun [__] at night while everybody's
sleeping so nobody bothers me. And the
cons of it is that
well there's really no con of it
honestly. I'm [__] I think I'm doing
pretty well, right? So I don't really
want to get too technical in this video
but pretty much GBP CAD has been
consolidating. So this the 4hour time
frame. So 48 12
4 + 12 16 + 4 is 20. So for the last 20
hours we've just been doing nothing. and
NZDUSD.
We've just pretty much been
consolidating for the last eight hours
and it looks like we're coming right
back into our entry and realistically if
the market's about to close on the
weekend. I don't believe in holding.
There's a long story behind that.
Honestly,
it gets lonely out here at night
sometimes.
>> Nobody's judging.
>> So, yeah, I just don't think the market
has enough movement now. And you know, I
wish the experience that I would have
now, I wish I knew it, you know, 2 3
years ago, I'd be so far ahead in my
journey, but I also feel like I would
have not known what to do with it
properly. I feel like I had to have gone
through the struggles that I had to go
through to be in sync and understand how
I am with the markets. Now, this is
actually the first week, I think, in
three months, ironically enough, right?
It happens to happen for the for the
video. It's the first week in three
months that I take two positions in one
single week. I'm the type of guy when I
trade that I just literally sit right
there at home base and you can pitch to
me 100 different balls and I'm just
going to wait, watch every single ball
pass by. If I don't get the perfect
pitch, I'm not going to swing. I don't
want to strike out. I want to keep
playing the game. The goal is to stay in
the game as long as you can and swing
when you get that right pitch. And if
that means I only take one trade every
two weeks, it is what it is. But best
believe every single time I take that
trade, I'm going to risk a [__] ton of
money behind it because I've been
waiting for it. And best believe when I
do enter it, I'm going to let it ride
and set and forget as as long as I
possibly can. And a lot of you guys,
what you guys do is you guys hurry up to
get to home base and the first pitch
that they throw you, you swing and you
strike. Then you're like, you know what?
I got to get my get back. They pitch you
the second ball, you strike. And then
now you say, you know what? They're not
going to be better than me. There's no
way I'm going to strike out. You swing
again. strike out. You need to be
patient in the game. The market is
literally going to throw you endless
amounts of opportunities. It's open
24/5. The market is literally meant to
operate whenever you want, but that
doesn't mean that you should. You should
only be trading when the time makes
sense and when the trade is ready. And
if that happens to be once a week, maybe
once every two weeks, it is what it is.
But when that perfect pitch comes, be
ready to swing the [__] out of it. And
if you're gonna swing and you hit it,
you run as fast as you can to first
base, second base, third base, and you
take it all the way home. That's exactly
what I do. If I take my trade, I'm going
to make sure I get the perfect entry,
risk a solid amount of money, and I hold
all the way to the takerit. If I waited
3 4 days for the perfect trade setup,
best believe I'll wait 3 4 days to
maximize the profits behind it. Not if I
go into some profit, I'm going to close
right away. The only reason why I'm
going to close right now is because I
don't want to hold throughout the
weekend because it's right on my entry
point and I believe market open of next
week with the spreads. It can either
take me out of my stop loss or I'm just
paying unnecessary fees for no reason
when I can get the same entry next week
at a better cost and with better
momentum. These are all just little
things that change trading completely
and it makes you avoid those unnecessary
losses and it makes you double down on
those wins. That's what's led me to
really be the profitable trader that I
am today. It's double down on what works
and avoid the [__] Everybody tries
to focus like literally when I get on
calls with my students, people are
always talking about, yo, okay, can you
explain to me, can you break down what
you don't look into a like what what
what don't you look at in a market for
you to avoid the trade? It's like, why
would I explain to you the endless
amount of possibilities of things that I
don't want when I can just only tell you
the one thing I do want? And it's so
much easier to find one thing that you
want than have an endless timeline and a
bunch of different markets that you can
look at [__] that makes no sense. So
these are all little things of tweaking,
little things of just being here every
single night for years and years and
years and hours and hours and hours that
led me to have a different aha moment.
Because there's an aha moment like, "Oh,
I get it now. That makes sense." to the
point where I'm now at like, oh, now I
know when to really deeply be involved
and when to not. So, this has been my
like literally I think the last 8 months
I've become the best trader that I've
ever became. And I think that's thanks
to the type of person that I am now.
When I go execute the market, I'm a lot
more nonchalant. I almost treat it like
a business decision. Every single
position I take, I make sure it's
actually worth it. And a great business
decision or a great business opportunity
doesn't come every day. And if anything
that maybe once a week. So we're going
to close this trade right now just for
the culture. So showing you guys right
here. This how we do it. 50. Hold on.
Let me screen record it for the haters
on uh social media.
Got to do it for the [__] haters.
This is the haters goals right here.
Their goal is to make $55,000 a month.
And I'm doing this on accident. Like I
am like this is like break even to me
almost. So we're going to come here.
Close bulk operations. Close all
positions. Close all our positions. 3.1
million on the account. Come here to our
total profit for the last four weeks.
894,000.
Pretty good. Pretty solid.
Not bad. Not bad. So, right now,
probably take a shower. Neil called me
before I came into here. So Neil works
late at night as well like me and he
told me, "Yo, pull up to pick up two of
my watches that he's been kind of
holding down for me cuz I don't really
like going to the office when there's a
lot of people there. So I'll probably
pull up to Neil maybe in like the next
30 minutes, 45 minutes, right at 2:00
a.m., pick up some watches, come right
back. That's pretty much a night. I'll
wake up maybe at 8 9 in the morning as
well." So I really will sleep just a
little bit at night, maybe, you know,
four or five hours. Wake up, do whatever
I have to do in the morning. And then
right at midday, I'll just like take a
2, three hour nap. maybe around three,
four in the afternoon sometimes when
it's traffic hour because I really don't
leave for traffic hour and then I
basically reset the day again. And on
the weekend, I literally spend 90% of my
time here at the house just doing stuff,
going to see family and just trying to
just relax because honestly staying up
like this every single night sometimes
it it just is mentally draining having
to just watch this [__] and just make a
decision off of it. So yeah, let's go
take a shower. pull up to Neil's place
and see where the night takes us.
>> Yeah. So, right now we're on our way to
Bickl to go pick up two of my watches.
Honestly, I didn't really have
another time to do it, and I rather just
do it right now at night since I'm
already pretty much uh
>> What do you call that when you stay up
at night?
>> What's up with this?
>> What's your name?
>> No, it's not it's not my car. All right.
Rent it. Is it actually?
>> Yeah. This shit's fire.
>> These are your boys.
>> Yeah. These are my boys.
>> Trying to get Tony.
>> It's loud as [__]
>> This shit's sick.
>> You want to hear it?
>> Did it shoot flames?
>> I don't know.
>> That thing's sick, bro.
>> Sick, bro. That's badass, bro.
Uh,
>> these guys doing awake at this time,
bro. What the [__] is going on, bro?
>> So random.
So, we're pulling up to Neil. So, Neil
is on pretty much the last floor up
there. You know who else is up there?
Steve. Steve is up there. He's probably
passed by Steve's house and he's up
there right now. Steve is literally on
the last penthouse. I tried renting the
apartment from him, but he doesn't want
to. He wants to stay with it.
>> Yo, right downstairs, brother.
>> Oh, but I actually came to my other
crib, bro.
>> Wow. I forgot you were coming.
>> I have your watch, though. I have the
watch. I have two watches for you. So,
wait, you're not here?
>> No, I left.
>> [__]
>> But just just come. It's right there.
It's 15 minutes. I just drove. There's
no traffic, bro.
>> Okay. Okay, I got you.
>> Black or red?
>> Red.
>> Black.
>> Yo, the house never [__] loses, bro.
>> There's something up with that watch,
>> bro. For real. What the [__]
>> If there's somebody that you can call at
3:00 in the morning just to chill on a
regular night, it's going to be this
guy.
>> You got it.
>> You got it on.
>> What is this? Is that Is it me?
>> Uh, it's uh Dana's energy drink.
>> Really?
>> Yes. A form energy. Buy it. You know, I
don't think it's real. It's something
that Bud Light used to do.
>> You don't think it's real? Diamonds?
>> Yeah. Like the Bud Light CEO gave
>> that [__] weighs though. gave this to uh
the Bud Light one to Dana and uh he gave
it to me and then uh someone broke in my
house.
>> Wait, so someone broke into your house
>> in Las Vegas? Yeah.
>> Oh, that's right. I remember.
>> Yeah. Have you guys seen this Sugar
Sean's belt?
>> That's actually Sugar Sean's belt.
>> Yeah, he gave it to me.
>> So, when you come when you come become
uh become UFC champion, they gave you
two belts and I was like the one of like
one of the first guys brought them out
in Miami like way back in the day. And I
remember just saying, "You're going to
be champion. You're going to be a
billionaire." This that and he he was
like a like nobody kind of. So yeah,
that's his real belt.
>> Like this is from the fight.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's his belt.
>> Yo, let you have the your roulette the
new one.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Let me see.
>> Damn, bro. That's a lot bigger than I
thought. Holy [__]
>> It's so bulky. See? Can I see that? See,
it's almost like like this one's like
worth like I guess a lot more you could
sell it for, but it's almost like um how
we're both at the same time.
>> Oh my god. Yeah,
>> dude. That [__] is so hard. Wait, did
this spin as well?
>> Yeah. Yeah, it spins. But I almost feel
like this one looks better.
>> No, bro. That one looks way better,
dude.
>> Like on on a on a red strap.
>> Oh, on a red strap. Yeah.
>> No, you have to get the red strap. It's
a It's way different.
>> Do you imagine wearing that?
>> You think I can wear this?
>> Do you want You want to wear it?
>> No. You think I can wear this? Um, I'm
filming a a vlog with David Dori, like
us like gambling like day in the life
phase. I'm send a bunch of stuff. This
one looks better, does it not?
>> No, bro. No, dude. That one is way
nicer.
>> Wait, can you wear it so I can see?
>> How do you want me to?
>> Yo, I like that one better like
lookswise, but this one costs a lot more
money.
>> Yeah,
>> dude.
I have to have both the whole thing. I'm
just going to blow David Dori's mind.
>> Oh, wait. Red Rock.
>> Red Rock everything.
>> Wait, what are you going to do?
>> Do you know that guy Papino on my
Instagram story?
>> Yes, bro. Pipino. Yeah, the fat guy.
Yeah,
>> bro. He's the coolest guy ever. He's the
eighth one in the world. You know my
friend Tommo, my Japanese guy.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> We're going to start off in Los Angeles
and I chartered like a big ass plane.
So, it's going to be like my squad is
me, Apino, Tommo, Uncle Tim, Donald
Trump, this guy I met in Brazil that
lives in Nicaragua, and Togei. Like, I I
assembled the Avengers of Degenerates
Alcoholics.
>> Bro, I I don't think David Dober is
ready for that, bro.
>> No, he's not ready. I don't know. I'm
just going to just like blow his mind
like we need to get to the airport. Hey,
but you want to go to Vegas? It's me,
Neil, Nelson, Vince. We're taking a jet.
Uh I'm only taking a jet cuz I have to
bring my dogs.
>> I I'll pitch him for
>> Oh, yeah. I got my N word revoked.
>> Why?
>> Uh white people revoked it. But yeah.
>> What? What? White people revoked that
for me, bro.
>> Companies. I'll get a new one. It's like
the the whites that don't [__] with it
and then like the black white people.
Like the black people are kind of, you
know what I'm saying?
>> All right, brother. Dude, enjoy your new
watch.
>> Thanks, dude.
>> How old are you guys, bro?
>> I'm 19.
>> 18.
>> 19.
>> [__] you guys.
>> We outside. We're in Tampa, bro.
Knocking doors out for a year.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Want to make it out, bro?
>> I mean, bro, just keep grinding, bro.
Keep pushing forward, bro. Like you guys
are so young, bro. Yo, when I was 18, I
was at Dunkin Donuts, bro. To see you
guys.
>> I know. I I peeped it. I seen it. Yeah,
I know. I see you, bro.
>> Follow, bro. I follow you and
everything. I seen you, bro.
>> But yeah, we see we see you like trying
to blow up the GT3 RS.
>> Yeah. No. Yeah, it blew up.
>> It actually blew up.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> But it's just like to a point like, you
know, money doesn't really matter you.
It's just like to a point like you I
don't know. I don't know how to explain
it. It's just like
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's like
>> it's like [__] you. Like this really
doesn't mean to me, but like I can show
people I can do it. You feel me?
>> And it's just really an inspiration
because like that's just where our
mental state is at. Like our mental
state is that like hustling and you
know, we just want to see how far we can
get and and you know, at a young age
doing this, we have higher risk and high
risk means low responsibility. So,
>> you know, we can do whatever we want, go
chase. That's why we want to get rich
fast. That's that's how it is. We want
to get rich fast and that's why but we
know at the end of the day it doesn't
doesn't work like that. So
>> thank you for everything you do.
>> Appreciate it, bro. For real.
>> You're a real inspiration, dog. Thank
you.
>> Can I take a picture for real? Like at
the front of the Lambo?
>> Jacob and Co. I seen I seen that [__]
the other day, bro. You posted it. I was
>> black or red? Black.
>> Black. Black. You sure?
>> Yeah.
[Music]
Red,
>> bro.
What the house never [__] and loses,
bro.
>> That's his favorite watch.
>> That's his favorite watch. What the [__]
is going on here?
>> Can you do it? Can you do it? Can you do
it? Let's do it right now.
>> What you putting on? What are you
putting on right here?
>> All right. Black or red?
>> I want to put on red. You
>> sure?
>> Yes. Red. It's going to be a 14. Nah,
you got to put that [__] on black.
>> It's on red.
>> All right. First guy. First guy. You
already know.
[Music]
>> Let's go find some ladies.
much money
dollar bill.
>> That [__] never gets old, bro. Ever.
>> I have 17 cars, so only one wouldn't
fit. But I'm going to get like a nice
indoor spot, bro.
>> Like a warehouse,
>> like a HQ for TPT. So, we'd meet there
right now, you know, like whenever I'm
not at the office and I'm working, I'm
like working in the house office. I I
would I would be
>> Why don't you get the the collections?
>> I'm looking. One of my clients owns one.
He's down to sell it to me. He's down to
rent it to me. He said he'll give me
prices and I'm going to think about it.
>> I don't know, bro. I'm just so busy.
It's like how much can we do at once?
>> I know. I mean, you usually like stay up
at night as well, right? Cuz I'm up like
the majority of the night.
>> What time do you get up in the morning?
>> Earlier than you. I know that. like 8 9
>> me like 10:30 11 nowadays
>> but it feels so late bro when you get up
at 11:00 like by the time I'm in the gym
it's 12 finish 1:30 I'm like bro
>> yeah but then there that's why you stay
up to like 2:00 3:00 in the morning and
[__]
>> later even this shit's gangster
>> how come you haven't had an SVJ
>> set and forget here
>> honestly I drove one one day alpha
slices do you remember
>> oh yeah and it blew up
>> it blew up so dude I'm like scarred bro
like I don't want one
>> you want to give this one a try Uh, I'd
give it a try.
>> It has 1,000 miles, bro.
>> All right, let's drive on it. Let's
drive it. We're going a bit.
>> No, no, but I'll show you.
>> I'll leave it here, bro.
>> My SF90.
>> Let me see your SF9. I haven't seen it.
>> I got to sell these hoes.
>> Oh, those are from the pizza
>> from this.
>> Oh,
>> I don't have a pista.
>> I'll show you. Yeah,
>> I wish I had a pista.
>> But you could afford a pizza.
>> I know. I wish I had one. You know I
won't buy one, right? Cuz I spent so
much on my 488.
>> Yeah. And I'm just like,
>> "Yeah, but that right there is like
where the safest money's at, bro." The
pizza,
>> dude, I don't [__] with these things,
bro.
>> That's what you're scared of?
>> I'm not scared.
>> Yo, come here. Yo, come here. Come here.
Come here.
>> I'm not scared, bro.
>> Yo, bro, look at the size of this thing,
bro.
>> Wait, you're not scared? So, come here.
>> I don't like frogs and [__] bro.
>> Dude.
>> All right. You want me to let him
outside?
>> Yeah, let him outside. Don't kill him.
Yes. Yeah. That that spec.
>> Oh, it came on my birthday.
>> Do you even drive that bike?
>> No, never.
>> You want it?
>> Honestly, you can take it. No cap.
>> Like I I never use it. If I ever want
it, I'll call you.
>> But is it is it gas or is it electric?
What is it?
>> It's electric.
>> Yeah, you can take it, bro. I don't use
it.
>> If you're If you're going to use it,
take it. And if I want it, I'll call
you.
>> No, I probably will never use it,
though. Yeah. Like guaranteed never use
that [__]
>> bro. I I have a I have a Harley-Davidson
in my garage. I've had it for 2 years.
I've never driven home. So,
>> bro, you did it. It's actually
>> pretty beautiful, bro.
>> Let me see the watch.
>> Pretty beautiful. I ain't going to lie.
So, you guys seen the who cares? I'm
already late Rolex. I'm sure it's like a
white and blue face. It's a date just
Alex went like big boss version. Day
date. When in doubt, # set and forget.
Super epic. And honestly, it looks so
beautiful, bro.
>> That's [__] sick, bro.
>> Yeah, that's [__] sick,
>> bro. You look so much better.
>> Yeah, cuz that that yellow face was
disgusting.
>> I agree.
>> Oh, bro, that looks m as [__]
>> Like when I saw you wearing this
sometimes, I was like, "Bro, that is not
for you."
>> Yeah, but this this does look like that.
>> Yeah. And if I want to go more gangster,
I could like baguettes on the on the
ring.
>> I wouldn't even touch it. It looks so
What do you think, Sebast?
>> I like it like that.
>> Clean like that. Right,
>> bro? So, they make a Onyx dial uh Rolex.
It's like 80K. Yours looks like that
from from like a distance. Look, check
this out. This is the Onyx, right? It
kind of looks similar, bro.
>> Bro, it looks I actually like how this
looks better
>> cuz it's you.
>> Yeah, cuz it's clean. Yeah,
>> it's pretty epic, bro.
>> Yeah, I like it. [__] yeah.
>> And And we made it new, too, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah, cuz the [__] was all clapped
up, dude. This is my watch for like
playing tennis.
>> It's not appropriate. You need like This
is a tennis watch, bro.
>> So, how much is that?
>> Uh 320,000.
>> It's a good tennis watch.
>> Humbling.
>> Very humbling. Very durable for tennis,
bro.
>> No, it's not a humble wig, bro. You got
you got the roulette table on your
wrist, bro.
>> Yeah. So, we have this one and then we
got this one as well.
>> Yeah, that's
>> the black. So,
>> black AP. You want me to explain it?
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> I got you.
>> It's a black ceramic. One of the
lightest materials ever used in watch
making. The entire case, the entire
bracelet, everything is black ceramic
here, guys. 41 mm open work. Honestly,
one of the sexiest watches out, bro.
>> I think I think this is one of the
sexiest APS
above the rose or the gold one that I
had, remember?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I feel like this is 100% more
gangster than that.
>> I It's beautiful, bro.
>> Is it Is it appropriate to wear three
watches at the same time?
>> No, don't do that.
>> You got hair though.
>> Oh, maybe one here if anything.
>> Yeah. No, no. I'm going to I rock the AP
on this.
>> Let Sebast rock one more.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm like,
>> here. Here. I got
>> How much How much is this?
>> He wears a big, bro. This one's 265,000.
This is worth around 50,000.
This watch is 280,000. This is
beautiful. Red or black? For how much?
Let's do one. Let's do one spin for fun.
We don't need to pull out cash. We're
good.
>> Okay. No, I was like have
>> But how much? How much money?
>> 100 bucks.
>> No.
>> Okay.
>> Yo, you we used to play poker here. You
remember? Uh at least 500.
>> At least 500. Yeah.
>> You You can Let me go red cuz red's my
favorite color.
>> Okay, fine.
>> Yeah. And you got a black watch today.
Two black watches.
>> Okay, fine. All right.
>> Black's coming out all day.
>> Okay, I'm going to mix it up first. I
>> I have to spin.
>> You spin. It's your watch.
>> Oh, you [__] up.
>> Yo. Yo, he's regular [__]
>> Look, it has a trick,
>> bro. You can't tilt, dude. Look, you're
going to you're going to spin or you're
going to leave it like this. Okay.
>> Wait, I'll leave it.
>> Yeah, leave it there and push it. Yeah.
>> Like that.
>> Some scam [__] bro.
>> 500 bucks.
>> I'm ready. You're black.
>> Some Vegas warm up, bro. It landed. It
lands green.
>> Wow.
>> So, you owe me a thousand.
>> No. Bro, it landed.
>> That's crazy, though. I've never seen it
on the watch. Swear.
>> That's why.
>> Yo, how many times have you spun the
watch and it's never landed on green,
>> bro?
>> I've never seen that either. And I've
sold quite a few of these, bro. Swear.
>> What the? Because it's not even a
two-sided green. It's
>> And I said warm up for Vegas, bro. Now,
maybe that's going to mean like we're
going to kill it in Vegas, bro.
>> Bro, that either means we're going to
kill it or we're gonna get [__] No,
no, no.
The other
>> Yeah. What's again? Red and black.
>> All right, fine.
>> That was boring.
>> Cool, but boring.
>> Yep.
>> Red.
>> Pay me, buddy.
>> Add it to the bill.
>> Let me show you. You've seen my other
office.
>> Let me see it.
>> I have more watches there.
>> Yeah. Couple.
>> Oh, bro. This is super gangster,
>> bro. Look how heavy that [__] is, bro.
Try to pick it up.
>> Oh my god.
>> Yo, who?
>> I bought it from Yaniv. You remember the
Jewish guy who who did like the braes
that lived in here?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He was moving out. I went to his
house cuz he called me over and I was
like, "Bro, you moving that?" He's like,
"Yeah." I'm like, "Can I buy it?" And I
just bought it off.
>> For how much?
>> I think it was 2 grand,
>> bro. I'll give you five grand.
>> I mean, if you want it. Yeah, sure. Take
it. Like five grand. Done deal.
>> I'm up 3500 right now, bro.
>> 3500.
>> Yo, what?
>> You can take it yet. You don't have to
either.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no. I I'm going to
figure out where I'm going to put it.
This is super
>> cuz I I don't want to sell it, but
that's a good profit.
>> It's like a 150% return, bro.
>> It's the Indian
I didn't say anything.
>> That's legendary bug shot.
>> Yeah,
>> bro. How do you know where everything's
at? Do you don't lose [__] sometimes,
>> bro? This came just now. Like uh Matthew
was here bringing it from a client. It's
going to go to the office tomorrow
morning.
>> That is fire.
>> Eye of the tiger Daytona.
>> Drake.
>> White gold.
>> Drake has this one.
>> Beautiful.
>> How much is this? I
>> think right around 200.
>> M. Don't quote me on that. Anyone if
this goes in the video, but
>> around there. Yeah.
>> I could see it on you. I could never see
that on me. It's so like
>> exotic,
>> brother. Yeah, I could rock this [__]
all day.
>> Yeah, on you. I can see it actually. I
don't know.
>> Eye of the tiger.
>> Look at this. This is insane, bro.
Strope edition.
>> Let me see.
>> 25 pieces in the world.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Yeah,
>> that's [__] hot.
>> Sold today.
>> Yeah, I love this.
>> That's fire.
>> Yeah, that's super fire. That's hot,
right?
>> Did they The gold face was wet?
>> Super gangster.
>> Yeah. Now, now what happens after this?
People start copying though, so other
people are going to start doing this
now. But it's okay.
>> No, I don't think so. It won't It won't
even come out as epic, bro. Like your
your your whole like what is it called?
slogan.
>> Your slogan fit perfectly right there,
you know.
>> Yeah.
>> You got the exact word I was thinking of
from Dori.
>> This is David.
>> Steve told you, right?
>> Yeah. He told me he's going to give a
watch.
>> Oh, that's hot.
>> Yeah. Everyone wants
>> You've always convinced me to try and
get this watch
>> here. Try it.
>> I remember I wore I wore it and
everything, but
>> the same one. Steel black. You wore the
nicer one. Mine?
>> Yeah. Yeah. The other one.
>> Yeah. Mine was like with the I think it
was gold with dual time zone. But this
is a really nice watch as a gift. You
know about the other gift that he's
getting from Togei?
>> No, I don't know it.
>> Oh, that [__] crazy.
>> Oh, wait. Wait. Toi is getting him
something.
>> Yeah, he bought it from me, bro. [__]
crazy gift. It's a car.
>> A car?
>> 720 Spider.
>> But like nice spec, bro. Like 2,000 mi.
202023.
Like
>> Oh, dude. He's not ready for that [__]
>> He spent like 300K.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But Steve is not ready for that.
>> No.
>> Like he he didn't see it coming, right?
>> I got him a gift, too, and it's not even
here yet. [__] annoyed. I showed it
to you or no?
>> Richard Mal chandelier full of baguette
cuz he gave his chandelier to toi then
he gave me that [__] crazy ass Rolex.
It's bro after he started with his
Supra. It's like I have to keep
>> Yeah.
>> But it's fun, bro. Honestly, with my
close friends, I like doing it. It's
fun.
>> Do you even drive the Supra?
>> No.
>> It's dead.
>> Yeah. Try starting it. It's dead.
>> Yeah. The battery, right?
>> It's been dead for like I want to say
like uh two months, bro. I got new in
them. What you need to do that with that
is get like the warehouse and that's
just like an art piece, bro. And just
leave it there.
>> Yeah. And it'll be plugged in and like
it could start when I wanted to. Like
right now, I don't even want to fix it
cuz bro, fix it, spend money, and then I
ain't going to drive it. It's going to
die again. I have so many cars in the
shop right now.
>> This thing's hard though.
>> You can take anything you want though.
It's your car. That has genti on it. The
A12.
>> Whatever you want. You pick
Bravis. Oh, you have a Brabus, right?
You You have a manser. Yeah.
Um,
>> you don't have anything manual, right?
>> No.
>> No. I'll take the SF9er.
[Music]
>> Bro, I'm tired, bro. This is
realistically how a random night in my
life goes. It's like the most random
[__] just happens every single night.
I don't know. I like like
I just pulled it to my friend's house
and I swapped super cars with him, bro.
Like, if it's all good. Say out here,
have my Lambo and we get your Ferrari.
It's all good. I don't know. I feel like
my 21-year-old self would have not
comprehended or understood how there's
like a whole different level to life and
success and how normal it can be once
you get there.
And I still feel like there's another
level.
and then another level and another one
and I still really feel like I'm only
getting started.
But these night routines is what's going
to get me to that next level.
Surrounding myself with successful
people, putting in the work and
following my training plan, taking the
risk when nobody else wants to. That's
what's going to take me to the next
level. I know
just being around like other rich
people, I feel so humbled, you know,
but far
It's pretty [__] fast, bro. Holy
[__] I don't You think Bugatti fast? I
don't know about Bugatti.
>> Probably not. I don't know about Bugatti
fast, but definitely fast as [__]
Nothing's like a Bugatti, bro.
[Music]
>> I'm tired
right now. Is that
>> Yeah. So,
>> night
>> pretty much what a night in my life
looks like. Honestly, I love it. Pretty
spontaneous and kind of just like me and
the guys and just like priority [__]
you know. I don't even know what I'm
saying anymore. I'm so
tired. Well, guys, I hope you guys
enjoyed this video. Make sure to hit
that like and subscribe button and we'll
see you boys in the next one.
>> I don't think this is the end of the
video at all.
>> Why is that?
>> It's not an IG video. If we don't drift,
>> you want to go. You want to go drift.
>> I mean, it's not what I want to do, but
it's what has to be done.
>> That's what we got to do, right?
But I feel like if we're going to do it,
we got to do it right.
Let's go do it [__] right.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Yo,
how are they still alive? Let's get out
of here.
Are they just throwing success in your
face? All of these batties obsessed with
my face. All they dress in my face. I
can't be showing no stress in my face.
No face. No face. No face. No face. No
face. No face. No face. No face. No
face. No face. No face. No face.
[Music]